(Howard:)Raj, you just
got a text.
(Howard:)The probe turned
on. It's fine.
(sighs)
Oh, good.
Namaste, Grandpa.
(Leonard:)I thought
this was gonna be boring,
(Leonard:)but it's actually kind of fun.
(Penny:)Don't tell Amy that. We'll
be here every Sunday.
(Amy:)Sheldon, that really is
an excellent basket.
(Sheldon:)It's not a basket.
(Sheldon:)It's a soldier's helmet
from 16th century China.
(Amy:)Very nice.
(Raj:)Yeah, it
looks great.
(Sheldon:)I saw that.
(Leonard:)Well, roomie,
it's only one night a week,
(Leonard:)but it's a start.
(Penny:)I know. I'm really
proud of Sheldon.
(Leonard:)Yeah, I'm proud of him, too.
SHELDON:
Can you keep it
down? Some of us
(Sheldon(in Penny's living room):)are trying
to sleep out here.